人人影视
YYeTs.com
原创翻译  双语字幕
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多影视更新
请登陆www.YYeTs.com
你被监视着
You are being watched.
■
・ 翻译  面条打包子
・ 翻译  紫玉
■
・ 翻译  板栗桑
政府有一套秘密系统
The government has a secret system--
■
・ 翻译  紫杉
・ 翻译  王小麦
一台每时每刻都在监控你的机器
a machine that spies on you every hour of every day.
■
・ 翻译  宅女之后
somehacker
我设计这台机器是为了侦测恐怖行动
I designed the machine to detect acts of terror
■
・ 翻&校  阿好
但它却看到了一切
but it sees everything--
■
压制  灰灰是菇凉
牵涉普通人的暴力罪行
violent crimes involving ordinary people.
Jessie  Sage  Kallen  吉吉  Jessie  Sage  Kallen  吉吉  Jessie  Sage  Kallen  吉吉  Jessie  Sage  Kallen  吉吉
■
时间轴
政府认为这些人无关紧要
The government considered these people irrelevant.
我们不
We don't.
受当局追捕  我们只能秘密活动
Hunted by the authorities, we work in secret.
你永远找不到我们
You'll never find us.
特效
灰灰
但无论是受害人还是行凶者
But victim or perpetrator,
总监
阿好
只要你的号码被列出来  我们就会找到你
if your number's up, we'll find you.
疑犯追踪
第三季 第二集
链接目标
一切就位
Everything's in place.
克鲁格  韦恩・L
很好  开始吧
Good, let's begin.
克鲁格  韦恩・L
他就这样
He does that.
注重隐私啊
The man likes his privacy.
女儿家试试无妨啊
You can't blame a girl for trying.
给你的
It's for you.
早上好  肖女士
Good morning, Ms. Shaw.
早
Morning.
适合散步的好天气
Beautiful day for a walk.
大概吧
I suppose.
你散完步  能否回图书馆跟我们会面
When you finish yours, could you join us back at the library?
有新号码了
We have another number.
卡尔文・T・比彻
英勇殉职
纽约警局警探
(1968年7月28日――2013年4月5日)
卡特警探  是吗
Detective Carter, right?
其实是警员了
Office actually.
阿伦佐・奎恩
Alonzo Quinn.
卡尔的教父  当然记得
Cal's Godfather, of course.
我在葬礼上见过你
I remember you from the funeral.
你写的悼词很棒
Your eulogy was beautiful.
因为卡尔本来就很棒
Wasn't hard to find beautiful things to say about Cal.
警长一直有向我汇报案件的进度
Chief was keeping me apprised of his case.
说他们怀疑开枪的人是卡尔・以利亚的手下
Says they're looking at a couple of Carl Elias' men as the shooters.
是啊  我也听说了
Yes, heard that too.
你另有看法
You think otherwise?
不确定  但是我认为没那么单纯
Not sure. But I think there is more to than that.
我该上班了
My shift is about start.
别误了你的事  很高兴又见到你  警官
Don't let me hold you up. It's nice seeing you again, Officer.
彼此彼此  保重
Me too. Take care.
是我
It's me.
我看卡特警员这边还有问题
I think we might still have a problem with Officer Carter.
怎么了
What's up?
问问卡尔一案的进展
Looking for news on Cal's case.
没听说有
I haven't heard any.
那数据库里呢
What about in the database?
-卡特  -我想自己查的
- Carter... - Look, I'd check myself,
但你知道他们取消了我的权限
but you know they pulled my access.
是啊  他们要是发现我越权查案
Yes, they will pull mine too if they catch me
我的权限也保不住
poking around a case I'm not assigned to.
拜托  这很重要
Come on, it's important.
好吧  等人少点儿
Ok. When it clears out a little.
谢了  弗斯科
Thanks, Fusco.
看到号码了  芬奇
I've got our number, Finch.
这家伙什么情况
What do you know about this guy?
韦恩・克鲁格  43岁  已婚  互联网业者
Wayne Kruger, 43, married, Internet entrepreneur,
"生活轨迹"公司的创始人
and founder of a company called "LifeTrace".
这是什么生意
And what's their business?
他们自称提供"搜人"服务
They marketed themselves as a "People Search" service,
用户可以用来查找
where their users can look up old friends or relatives
生活轨迹
失去联系的亲友
anyone they've fallen out of touch with.
听起来没什么问题
Sounds harmless enough.
实际上  并非如此
There is, however, more to it than that.
想来也是
Always is.
这生意的重点不在帮人们取得联系
Their business isn't really about reconnecting people,
而是收集并出售人们的信息
it's about collecting and selling their information.
他是个数据掮客
He's a data broker.
什么数据
What kind of data?
你想知道的关于某个人的一切
Anything you would ever wanna know about a person
在何处居住  工作  购物  饮食
where they live, work, shop, eat,
收入多少  投票给谁  以及其他
how much they earn, how they vote and more.
然后他把这些信息打包卖给企业  个人
Then he turns around and sells the information to businesses, individuals
甚至政府
even the government.
这合法吗
Is that legal?
技术上说  数据掮客从公开记录中获取信息
Technically, data brokers get their information from public records,
但其实是收集人们在网上泄露的数据
but also from the ways people reveal themselves online
有些是透明的  有些是私下的
whether they're aware or whether they're not.
听起来有点像你的机器
Sounds a little like your machine.
二者有本质差异
A principle difference would be
机器从未泄露任何信息
that the machine never reveals any of its information
只给社保号码
beyond the social security number.
看来你不怎么喜欢克鲁格
So you're not a fan of Kruger's.
就是因为他这种人
People like him are one of the reasons
我才把机器设计成不可侵入的黑盒
I made sure the machine was impenetrable black box.
克鲁格刚刚进大厦了
Kruger's just entered his building.
现在交给肖了
He's in Shaw's hands now.
我希望让她进去的决策是正确的
I hope sending her in there was a good decision.
你担心她不够谨慎
You doubt her ability to be discreet?
我担心她忍不住拿枪突突人
I doubt her ability to keep from shooting someone?
复制手机
韦恩・克鲁格
强制配对
完成
复制手机
韦恩・克鲁格
强制配对
完成
我进来了  芬奇
I'm in, Finch.
克鲁格有个重要会议
Kruger's got some kind of big shot meeting.
先生们  贵方能考虑与我方合作  令我们深感荣幸
Gentlemen, we're thrilled that you're considering us.
我们知道里弗顿公司是零售巨头
We know that Riverton is a huge retailer
想要挑选潜在的数据合作方
and that you've got your pick of potential data partners.
我们也做了调查
We've done our homework--
或者说彼得帮我们做了调查
or rather Peter has done our homework, and
他说我们应该考虑你们公司
he says you're one of the companies we should consider.
我已经看过了你提供的所有信息
I've looked at all the information you provided,
包括公司的利润  增长率
including the company profile, growth rate,
顾客分析数据  目标数据点
consumer analytic statistics, and data points per target--
恭喜
Congratulations.
你的身份没问题吧  肖女士
Any problems with your cover, Ms. Shaw?
别叫我打字就不会暴露
Not unless someone asks me to type.
摇铃
A baby rattle?
如果我剧透了惊喜  抱歉
I apologize if I spoiled the surprise.
不  没事  只是  我跟妻子
No, it's all right, it's just, my wife and I
只对家里人说了  没对外公布
haven't told anybody outside the immediate family.
-你怎么知道的  -你的葡萄酒消费
- How did you know? - Your wine consumption.
-什么  -从以前的一周两瓶
- Excuse me? - It's dropped from two bottles a week
下降到过去的三个月几乎一瓶没有
to almost nothing in the past three months,
而你的牛奶  酸奶和奶酪消费却是之前的三倍
And your milk, yogurt, and cheese consumption has tripled.
你购物的那家商店
The grocery store where you shop.
你是他们"顾客忠诚项目"的会员
You're members of their customer loyalty program.
那项目是我们做的
We created that.
我还以为他们就发优惠券呢
And I thought they just sent out coupons.
不  这种项目
No. Programs like that
不过是冰山一角
are just scratching the surface of what we can do.
我们"生活轨迹"真正的方向
What we're really working towards here at LifeTrace
是未来
is the future,
未来  所有人的需要都将被满足
a future where every person's needs will be met
因为我们有所有必要的信息
because we have all the information necessary
满足其需要
to meet those needs.
以饮食习惯来预测疾病
Eating habits to predict diseases.
以相配分析来消除孤身
Compatibility factors to eliminate loneliness.
其方式就是了解一个人
And the way we do that is by getting to know someone,
上至生命中的大事件
from the major events of their lives,
下至日常生活中的点点滴滴
right down to the tiniest detail of their everyday routine.
全面了解一个人
Learning everything about a person
让我们得以帮助他们提升生活品质
allows us to help them improve their life.
似乎挺吸引人  但能否问下
Sounds appealing, but can I ask,
你们是否有过侵犯隐私的问题呢
have you run into any issues with respect to privacy concerns?
没什么大不了的
Nothing significant.
总有些人看我们做的事不顺眼
There are always a few who take issue with what we do,
不过  现在  众所周知  科技是无法抗拒的
but these days, people know, you can't fight the technology.
坦白说  那些成天叫着隐私权的
And let's be honest, those crying the loudest about privacy
多半藏着见不得人的事
are probably the ones trying to hide something.
因此  巴里
That's why-- uh, Barry.
-好的  -因此我把我的个人资料放到了网站上
- Oh, yeah. - That's why I put my own profile up on our site.
任何人都可以看到  我没有见不得人的
Anyone can look me up and see, I've got nothing to hide.
我们需要个提案呈交董事会
We'll need to work out a proposal to present to our board.
明天上午可以吗
How would tomorrow morning work for you?
挺好
Sounds great.
对  全是他们的号码
Yes, it'll be all their numbers--
不管这家伙出什么事儿
Whatever's going on with this guy,
他的生意倒是毫发无伤
it sure isn't hurting his business.
我想应该细查查克鲁格先生了
I think it's time to look a little more closely at Mr. Kruger.
那些号称"没有见不得人"的人  往往都有
People who say they have nothing to hide almost always do.
纽约州身份数据库搜索
搜索  韦恩・克鲁格
纪录上查不出什么
Nothing comes up on his record.
感谢帮忙
Thank you for checking.
我知道你现在上回白班了
I understand you're back on the day shift.
是啊  不过我有所舍弃了
Yeah, but I'm giving up something.
舍弃什么了
What's that?
耐心
My patience.
早上好
Good morning.
走着瞧吧
We'll see.
巡逻前  我想先说一声
Before we roll, I just want to say
我真的非常期待跟你一同
I'm really looking forward to working together and--
拉斯基
Laskey,
第一  我并不想当教习警员
one, I didn't want to be an F.T.O.,
但总好过昼伏夜出
but it beats being a vampire.
第二
Number two,
我让你干什么  你就干  别多问
when I tell you to do something, just you do it, no questions.
第三
And number three,
不许碰无线电  明白吗
don't touch my radio. Got it?
是  女士
Yes, Ma'am.
卡特  叫卡特就好
Carter. Just Carter.
我被困在办公室算怎么一回事儿
How is it I got stuck being the office monkey?
我还以为你喜欢参与行动  肖
I thought you liked being in the middle of the action, Shaw.
在收费站上班都比这"行动"刺激
I think I'd see more action in a tollbooth.
我只是想倒垃圾
I was just emptying the trash.
没关系
No problem.
-我一会儿回来  -好的
- I'll come back. - Okay.
通知董事会明天开会
Tell the board we're meeting tomorrow.
好的  克鲁格先生
Sure thing, Mr. Kruger.
摇铃那招太闹噱头
Quite a stunt you pulled with the baby rattle.
我该提前告诉你一声
I'd have told you about it,
但你肯定不让我送
but you'd have tried to talk me out of it.
没错  这笔生意一定要拿下
You're right. We need this deal.
我们拿下了  得了  巴里
Well, we just got it. Come on, Barry.
这将改变一切  让我们一步登天
This changes everything. This puts us on the map.
怎么了  海莉
What is it, Haley?
是今晚的派对
It's about the party tonight.
我想用您的信用卡预订
I tried to put the restaurant deposit on your credit card
但交易被拒绝
but it was declined.
什么  为什么
What? Why?
不知道  银行不说原因  很抱歉
I don't know, the bank wouldn't tell me, I'm sorry.
我来处理
I'll handle it.
有时候我真希望自己的助理
You know, sometimes, I wish I had an assistant
除了屁股辣之外还能有点儿实力
whose qualifications extended beyond having a great ass.
我真希望这家伙是行凶者
I sure hope this guy's a perpetrator.
想去派对吗  肖
Want to go to a party, Shaw?
只要你肯穿得娇媚点儿
Only if you promise to wear something pretty.
谢谢  你
Thanks. You.
首先  非常感谢各位
First, I want to say it's great of all of you
今晚大驾光临  尤其是我妻子迪迪
to make it tonight, especially my wife Dedee.
里瑟先生  克鲁格的派对怎么样
Mr. Reese, how's the Kruger's party?
令人愉快
Delightful.
有发现吗
Have you learned anything?
克鲁格朋友挺多
Just that Kruger's got a lot of friends,
婚姻看起来挺幸福
appears to be happily married,
肖喜欢松露鹌鹑蛋
and Shaw likes truffled quail eggs.
你不能指望我饿着肚子开枪打人啊
You can't expect me to shoot somebody on an empty stomach.
我只希望你别开枪打人
I'd prefer you didn't shoot anyone at all.
你呢  芬奇  有发现吗
What about you, Finch? Dig anything up?
有  克鲁格处理了很多
Yes. Kruger's gone to great lengths
对"生活轨迹"不利的消息
to suppress any bad publicity about LifeTrace.
"生活轨迹"搜索结果
"生活轨迹"不肯撤下我的资料
"生活轨迹": 你的信息安全吗
我有暴力倾向的前男友通过"生活轨迹"找到了我
"生活轨迹"背后的谎言
"生活轨迹"在偷窃你的数据
谁来监控"生活轨迹"
爆料贴子  负面新闻
Negative blog posts, news articles,
还有个联合起诉案  签了保密协议私了
Even a class action lawsuit buried in non-disclosure agreements,
页面无法打开
网上都被清干净了
All scrubbed from the internet.
亲爱的  我爱你  这是献给你的
Sweetheart, I love you. This is for you.
韦恩与迪迪  15年爱情路
? Falling in love is something ?
? Falling in love is nothing ?
谎言
忠 诚
生活轨迹
韦恩・克鲁格
我没有见不得人的
I've got nothing to hide.
关掉  快关掉
Turn it off. Turn it off, now!
隐 私
安 全
关掉
Turn it off!
这是谁的恶作剧吗
This somebody's idea of a joke?
迪迪  亲爱的  我不知
Dedee, honey, I have no id--
里瑟先生
Mr. Reese?
在  有人把克鲁格的周年纪念光盘换成了性爱录像
Yeah, someone just turned Kruger's anniversary video into a sex tape.
天呐
Oh, my.
亲爱的  听我
Sweetie, listen--
你们看什么看
What are you all looking at?
回家去  派对结束了
Go home. The party's over.
派对结束了
Party's over!
这下越来越有意思了
Just when things were getting interesting.
是啊  先是信用卡  再是这个
I know, first his credit cards, now this.
有人在整克鲁格  芬奇
Someone's messing with Kruger, Finch.
要只是想羞辱他
The machine wouldn't send us his number
机器是不会给出号码的
if someone just wanted to humiliate him.
没错  我们得找到幕后人
No, we need to find whoever's behind this
免得他们对他下手
before they come after him again.
或者说免得克鲁格先找到他们
Or before Kruger finds them first.
-芬奇  -肖女士  没问题吧
- Finch. - Ms. Shaw. Is everything all right?
别这么紧张  哈罗德  我还没揍人呢
Don't sound so worried, Harold. I haven't hurt anybody...yet.
真宽心啊  有新消息
Very reassuring. You have news?
我知道昨晚是谁搞乱克鲁格的周年纪念了
I think I know who hijacked Kruger's anniversary party.
这是昨晚酒店的监控录像
Here's the restaurant's security camera footage from last night.
那女人穿得像服务生
A woman dressed as a waiter.
但所有的服务生以前从没见过她
None of the waitstaff had seen her before.
我见过
I might have.
我一直在查看联合起诉
I've been going through all the parties
克鲁格一案里所有的原告
to the class action suit against Kruger.
他们都声称私人信息
All of them claim to have been victimized
被"生活轨迹"泄露  深受其害
when their personal information was released by LifeTrace.
怎么害的
Victimized how?
身份盗用  骚扰  勒索  欺诈
Identity theft, harassment, blackmail, fraud.
甚至被谋杀
Even murder.
谁
Who?
克洛伊・哈珀
Chloe Harper,
首席原告雪利・哈珀的女儿
Daughter of the lead plaintiff, Sherry Harper.
她被人跟踪杀害
She lost her life to a stalker,
那人通过生活轨迹找到了她的住址
who found her home address using LifeTrace.
难怪克鲁格要把案子私了
No wonder Kruger wanted the suit buried.
现在弗斯科警探正在
Detective Fusco is running background checks
对所有原告进行背景调查
on all of the plaintiffs as we speak.
等等  我发现那神秘服务员了
Wait, I just found our mystery waiter.
她叫凯伦・米尔斯  住在皇后区
Her name is Karen Mills. She lives in Queens.
我这就去
I'm on my way.
不用  待在那儿  肖女士
No, stay put, Ms. Shaw.
我看看卡特警探能否帮忙
I'll see if Detective Carter can help us.
-她怎么了  -闯了停止标志
- What did she do? - Rolled a stop.
真的吗
Really?
待在车里  我来
Stay in the car. I got this.
请出示驾照和行驶证
License and registration, please.
有问题吗  警官
Something wrong, Officer?
纽约州驾照
凯伦・米尔斯
可以这么说
You could say that.
为什么要整韦恩・克鲁格
Why are you coming after Wayne Kruger?
别让我问第二遍   米尔斯女士
Don't make me ask twice, Ms. Mills.
我  我收到个包裹
I-I got a package.
包裹  谁寄来的
A package? From who?
我不知道
I don't know.
是匿名的
It was anonymous.
里面有张碟  还有写明
There was a DVD and some instructions
如果我想报复他应该怎么做
on what to do if I wanted to get back at him.
为什么  他对你做了什么
Why? What did he do to you?
他毁了我的生活
He ruined my life.
怎么毁
How?
我本来在一家律所做助理
I was a paralegal at a law firm.
在那儿认识了我的未婚夫
It's where I met my fiance.
一天  有助理律师
One day, some of the assistants were
通过那个网络找人  "生活轨迹"
looking people up on this website, LifeTrace.
他们发现了一些照片
They found some pictures.
什么照片
What kind of pictures?
是我前男友拍的
They were taken by an ex-boyfriend,
我们俩  在卧室里
of us, in his bedroom.
所有人都看到了
And everyone saw them.
我未婚夫  他
My fiance, he...
解除了婚约
called off our engagement.
我收到包裹时
When I got the package,
觉得终于能让克鲁格
I saw a chance to make Kruger
感受到我曾受的羞辱
feel the humiliation that I felt.
所以我做了
So I took it.
好吧
Okay.
这次就警告放行了  米尔斯女士
I'm gonna let you off with a warning this time, Ms. Mills.
但你得把你收到的包裹
So long as you take that package you got
拿去给第八局的莱奈尔・弗斯科警探
take it to a Detective Lionel Fusco at the 8th precinct,
并保证下不为例
and you promise me you'll never do anything like that again.
谢谢  不会了  警官
Thank you. I won't, Officer.
很好  因为纽约警局会发现的
Good, 'cause the NYPD, we'll know.
相信我
Trust me.
希望你听到了
Hope you got that.
里瑟先生
Mr. Reese?
我听到了
I heard.
听上去她和其他
Doesn't sound like she had anything to do
对克鲁格的攻击无关
with the other attacks on Kruger.
很可能是寄匿名包裹的人干的
Likely done by whoever sent the anonymous package.
宝贝  我知道你很生气
Look, baby, I know you're mad,
但请回我电话
but I need you to call me back.
银行说我们的卡被取消了
The bank says our cards have been canceled
我们的账户也被清空了
and our account's emptied out.
事情不对劲  给我回电
Something's wrong. Just call me.
海莉  能接通我会计的电话吗
Haley, will you get my accountant on the line?
你在干什么  有什么问题吗
What are you doing? What's the problem?
我的问题
My problem?
第一条留言
First saved message.
有时候我真希望自己的助理
You know, sometimes, I wish I had an assistant
除了屁股辣之外还能有点儿实力
whose qualifications extended beyond having a great ass.
-你从哪里听来的  -明显是从你这里
- Where did that come from? - You, apparently.
有人用克鲁格自己的话攻击他自己
Someone is using Kruger's own words against him.
他的办公室肯定被窃听了
His office must be bugged.
去死吧  韦恩
Screw you, Wayne.
海斯先生
Mr. Hayes?
科利尔先生
Mr. Collier.
科利尔先生  怎么了
Mr. Collier, what's going on?
鉴于近期的事态
In light of recent developments,
迪弗先生认为"生活轨迹"
Mr. Deaver doesn't think LifeTrace
并非我们需要的合作伙伴
is the best partner for us, after all.
失陪了
Excuse me.
这下子更好玩儿了
This is getting better by the minute.
到底怎么回事
What the hell happened?
我倒指望你解释一下呢
I was hoping you could tell me.
不不不不  得赶紧把这个撤下来
No. No, no, no. You gotta take the site down.
已经撤了  但是里弗顿公司已经看到了
We already did, but not before Riverton saw it.
他们撤销了合作
They yanked the deal!
真不敢相信
I cannot believe this is happening!
你从没说过你破产过  还有酒驾纪录
You never said you went bankrupt, or had a DUI.
那都是十年前的事儿了  早删除了
That was over ten years ago. It was expunged.
这是逮捕令吗
Is this an arrest warrant?
我那时在上大学  早撤销了
I was in college. It was dismissed.
这都是陈年往事了
Look, this is all ancient history.
对我们是新闻  对里弗顿公司也是
It's new to us, and to Riverton.
有人在故意整我  你看不出来吗
Someone is screwing with me. Can't you see that?
韦恩  我们认为你最好
Wayne, we think it might be best if you...
先花点时间处理一下个人问题
took some time to sort out your personal issues.
花点时间
If I took some time?
我们评估决策时  先暂时离职
A leave of absence while we evaluate our options.
你们评估决策
While you evaluate your options?
这是我的公司  巴里
This is my company, Barry!
你是公司的门面  问题就出在这里
And you're the face of it. And that's now a problem.
听着
Okay, look--
我们已经投票了
We already took a vote.
好吧  好吧
Fine. Fine.
但我会找出是谁干的
But I'm gonna find out who's doing this to me.
然后  我会打电话给里弗顿公司
And then, I'm gonna call Riverton.
我会解决
I'm gonna fix this.
克鲁格刚刚被赶出了自己的公司
Looks like Kruger's just been kicked out of his own company.
克鲁格的处境越发困难了  芬奇
Things are escalating with Kruger, Finch.
查出行凶者了吗
We any closer to finding the perpetrator?
正在找  里瑟先生
I'm working on it, Mr. Reese.
未知号码
来电
你好
Hello.
你伤害了很多人  克鲁格先生
You've hurt a great many people, Mr. Kruger.
什么  你是谁
What? Who is this?
你需要明白
You need to understand.
明白什么
Understand what?
你给我听好了  要是让我查出是你在
You listen to me. If I find out you're the one responsible--
电梯在自由落体
The elevator's free falling.
现代电梯不会自由落体  肖女士
Modern elevators do not free fall, Ms. Shaw.
跟克鲁格说去
Tell that to Kruger.
谎 言
科技是无法抗拒的
You can't fight the technology.
侵 犯
贪 婪
有人终止了自动保护系统
Somebody has disabled the auto-safety features.
电梯并不联网  我弄不到权限
The elevators aren't networked. I can't access them.
隐 私
贪 婪
生活轨迹
克鲁格逃出来了  芬奇
Kruger made it out, Finch.
要整他的人已经毁了他的公司
Whoever's coming after him has taken his company,
他的钱  他的婚姻
his money, his marriage.
剩下能毁掉的  只有他的命了
Soon the only thing left to take will be his life.
芬奇  他在电梯里接到的那个电话
Finch, the call he got in the elevator,
你能追踪来源吗
could you trace it?
不能  但不管是谁侵入了电梯
No, but whoever hijacked the elevator
肯定有大楼电配间的权限
would have needed access to the building's electrical room.
我倒是知道谁清了克鲁格的银行账户
I do know who cleaned out Kruger's bank accounts.
-谁  -丹尼斯・鲍尔森
- Who? - Dennis Paulson.
弗斯科警探从假身份证上弄出了他的照片
Detective Fusco got his photo off the phony ID.
他取空了克鲁格的帐户
He used to cash out Kruger's accounts.
他也是联合起诉克鲁格的人之一
He's another member of the class action suit against Kruger,
和米尔斯女士一样
same as Ms. Mills.
这么说是有多名行凶者了
Then we're looking at multiple perpetrators.
是的  鲍尔森丢了工作又被捕入狱
Yes. Paulson lost his job and was arrested
因为生活轨迹公司把他的资料
after LifeTrace conflated his profile with
跟另一个同名的连环强奸犯弄混了
that of a serial rapist who happened to have the same name.
最恨这种
Hate it when that happens.
鲍尔森告诉弗斯科  他从一个匿名包裹里
Paulson told Fusco he'd received the fake ID.
收到了假身份证和克鲁格的银行信息
and Kruger's banking information in an anonymous package.
和凯伦・米尔斯一样
Same as Karen Mills.
有人向受害者提供信息
Someone's giving these victims everything
让他们用来报复克鲁格
they need to get back at Kruger.
一站式复仇服务
It's turnkey revenge.
有多少人联合起诉
How many people in that class action?
超过两百  其中二十三人来自三角洲区域
Over 200. 23 in the tri-state area.
芬奇  这么多人我们可阻止不了
Finch, we can't stop that many.
试试倒也有趣
It'd be fun trying.
不过我得问问  这家伙值得我们浪费时间吗
I gotta ask, though, is this guy even worth our time?
我们救你的时候可没想过这个问题
You know, that's not a question we entertained when we saved you,
肖女士
Ms. Shaw.
要救克鲁格  只能先找到他
Our only chance to save Kruger is to find him.
我把他的坐标发给你
I'm sending you his coordinates.
他是北区石岩帮的成员
Guy's a member of the Northside Killas.
见鬼  乱枪射杀
Dang, got shot up pretty bad.
你觉得是谁干的
Who do you think did this?
不好说
Hard to say.
要我会先和他的客户谈谈
I'd talk to his regular customers first,
看他和谁有过节
see who he was having problems with.
但这不是我们的活儿
But that's not our job.
我们只需要看管好现场  记好笔录
We just secure the scene and take the statements.
是啊
Right.
第一次见死尸
First body?
是啊
Yeah.
你还好吗
You okay?
是啊  还行
Yeah, fine.
菜鸟
Rookies.
我不知道刚才怎么回事
I don't know what happened.
不知道  看看你的鞋啊
No? Take a look at your shoes.
吃你的冰块吧
Just suck on the ice.
查出什么了吗
You find anything?
我还没看呢  等等
I haven't looked yet. Hang on.
凶杀案  调查中
我瞧瞧
Let's see.
■
- - 文件受限 - -
- - 访问被拒绝 - -
怎么了
What is it?
文件被冻结了
The file's been frozen.
什么  为什么
What? Why?
你觉得呢  多半是隔墙有耳
Why do you think? Probably too many prying eyes.
我觉得好多了
I'm feeling a little better,
如果你想回去
so if you want to get back to it--
当然  走吧
Yeah, sure. Let's go.
行了  芬奇  我找到他了
Okay, Finch, I've got him.
科利尔先生  还是我  韦恩・克鲁格
Mr. Collier, it's Wayne Kruger again.
我非常希望在你离开之前  我们能见一面
I'm really hoping that we can meet before you leave town
我可以解释下之前的误会
so I can explain the confusion earlier today.
如果你给我个机会  我保证可以解决这事
If you give me a chance, I'm sure we can sort this all out.
那些成天叫着隐私权的
Those crying the loudest about privacy
多半藏着见不得人的事
are probably the ones trying to hide something.
谎言
芬奇
Finch.
他们黑进车里了
They've hacked the car.
安全
科技是无法抗拒的
You can't fight the technology.
侵犯
有人控制了
Someone is overriding
车辆的电控元件
the vehicle's electronic control unit.
科技是无法抗拒的
You can't fight the technology.
里瑟先生  他们可以控制
Mr. Reese, they can take control
他的转向和油门
of his steering and throttle.
要搭顺风车吧
Bet you could use a lift.
我在哪儿
Where am I?
一个你不会被那些
Somewhere you won't be attacked
想杀你的人攻击的地方
by the people who are trying to kill you.
你们是谁
And you are?
现在  是你的唯一选择
Right now, your only option.
我的车  发生什么了
My car, what happened?
这个电控元件
This electronic control unit,
控制了车辆的内部电控元件
it overrode your car's internal E.C.U.,
让别人可以远程控制你的车
allowing someone to control the vehicle's functions remotely.
别人是谁
Someone who?
联合起诉你的原告之一
One of the members of that class action suit brought against you.
那诉讼案  我的律师达成和解了
That suit? My lawyers settled that.
看来并非人人满意
Not to everyone's satisfaction, it would seem.
有意思
That's interesting.
怎么了
What?
克洛伊・哈珀  被人跟踪谋杀的年轻女士
Chloe Harper, the young woman killed by her stalker.
她的母亲是首席原告  但是没提到她父亲
Her mother was lead plaintiff, but there was no mention of her father.
我刚刚查了下他
I just looked him up.
斯图・萨默斯
Stu Sommers.
克洛伊没跟他姓  离婚了吗
Different last name than Chloe's--divorced?
我在大厦里见过这个男人
I remember that man from your building.
他是清洁工
He was posing as a janitor.
是  卡尔  没来多久
Yeah, Carl, hasn't been around that long.
因为三个月前  他还是
Because until three months ago, he worked
一家航空航天研究所的电子工程师
as an electrical engineer at an aerospace firm.
既然有这层背景  他有能力
With a pedigree like that, he would have the skills
策划如此周密的攻击
to design these sophisticated attacks.
我们得找到他
We need to find him.
他肯定在城里
He must be staying somewhere in the city.
他的人事档案  应该会有住址
His personnel file, it would have to have an address.
我明早打个电话去查
I can call tomorrow morning.
没必要
Not necessary.
巴克莱街250号
你黑进了我公司的服务器
Are you hacking my building's servers?
你介意吗
Do you mind?
卡尔・米勒  布鲁克林威洛斯街162号四公寓
Carl Miller, 162 Willow Street, apartment 4, Brooklyn.
他不在家里  就在"生活轨迹"公司
He'll either be there or he'll be at LifeTrace,
那里他有权限接入电脑系统
where he has access to the computers.
计划下一次攻击  我去公司查
Planning his next attack. I'll check it out.
我去公寓
I'll hit the apartment.
休息一下吧  克鲁格先生
Perhaps you should rest, Mr. Kruger.
今天可不容易
You've had quite a day.
有什么吃的吗
Got anything to eat around here?
只有煎绿茶  还有狗粮
Just sencha green tea and a box of doggie treats.
你在那儿忙活的事情
I don't suppose what you're working on
应该和我无关吧
over there concerns me.
我在用三角定位查找
I'm trying to triangulate the location
在电梯里给你打电话的人
of the call you received in the elevator.
你听得出声音吗
Did you recognize anything about the caller?
不  不能
No, nothing.
你最好别这么做
I'd prefer you didn't do that.
你最好别管闲事
I'd prefer you mind your own business.
真讽刺  干这行的人说出这话
That's a tad ironic, coming from a man of your profession.
-什么意思  -意思是你的职业
- Meaning what? - Meaning your business
就是管别人的闲事
is minding everyone else's business.
我的工作让人们生活更便捷更有质量
I do what I do to simplify and improve other people's lives.
你又做什么呢
What is it that you do?
帮助他人脱离困境
We help people out of difficult situations,
即使那人是自作自受
even situations of their own design.
那神经病想杀我  还是我的错了
So it's my fault that some wacko's trying to kill me?
他失去了女儿  克鲁格先生
The man lost his daughter, Mr. Kruger,
有人用你的服务跟踪她  杀了她
to a stalker who was aided by your service.
难道你觉得自己没有责任吗
You feel no accountability?
这产业的年产值高达三千亿  我只是其中一员
I'm part of a $300 billion-a-year industry.
信息被滥用很不幸  但就是这样
Information abuses are unfortunate, but they happen.
-无法阻止  -可以阻止
- Can't be helped. - Oh, they can,
只要有权限拿到这些信息的人
but only if the people who have access to the information
愿意积极保护这些信息
are as interested in protecting it
如同积极牟利一般
as they are in profiting from it.
我想看看我妻子有没有打电话
I was just checking to see if my wife had called.
我想确认她没事
I want to make sure she was okay.
克鲁格先生  我不希望你打电话
Mr. Kruger, I didn't want you using the phone
因为这不安全
because it might not be safe,
但如果你要查看信息
but if you must check your messages,
我们可以用运营商的网络门户
we can go through your phone carrier's web portal.
需要密码吗
Need my password?
你有一条信息
You have a message.
克鲁格先生  我是彼得・科利尔
Mr. Kruger, Peter Collier.
我和同事商量了
I spoke with my colleagues and
他们同意我们再次会面了
they agreed we should all sit down again.
如果你九点半前到梅菲尔德酒店
If you could meet us at the Mayfield at 9:30,
我们就能在起飞前见上一面
that should give us enough time before our flight.
我们在东餐厅等你
We'll meet you in the east dining room.
太好了  我现在离开  还能赶上
Yes, yes! If I leave now, I can still make it.
那你妻子呢
And what about your wife?
我在路上给她打电话
I'll call her on the way.
克鲁格先生  等等
Mr. Kruger, wait.
这条信息没有"新信息"标签
The message, it's not labeled as "New".
肯定是有人先听过了
Someone else must have listened to it first.
谁
Who?
萨默斯
Sommers!
如果是他  他会在酒店那儿等着你
And if he's listened to it, he'll be waiting for you at the hotel.
太危险了
It's too dangerous.
我不管  这笔生意太重要了
I don't care, there's too much riding on this deal.
好吧  我联系我的同伴
All right, I'll contact my associates,
让他们去酒店跟我们会面
then have them meet us at the hotel.
好了  好了  小熊
Okay, okay, Bear.
天啊
Goodness.
芬奇
Finch.
里瑟先生  克鲁格跑了
Mr. Reese... Kruger's gone.
我真不该对他掉以轻心
I made the mistake of turning my back on him.
你还好吧
Are you all right?
会好的
I will be.
看来小熊撕咬过克鲁格
It would appear that Bear slowed Kruger down.
他正在去梅菲尔德酒店的路上
He's making his way to the Mayfield Hotel
要跟里弗顿公司的人见面
to take a meeting with the Riverton people.
萨默斯应该也知道这事
I believe that Sommers knows that as well.
我找到他的储物柜了
I'm at his locker now.
他一直在跟踪克鲁格
He's been stalking Kruger,
正如他的女儿被跟踪
just like his own daughter was stalked.
并最终下杀手
And ultimately killed.
我马上去梅菲尔德酒店
I'll get over to the Mayfield.
还有  里瑟先生
Something else, Mr. Reese.
克鲁格不仅是受害者
Kruger's not only a potential victim,
现在可能还成了行凶者
he may also now be a perpetrator.
克鲁格  韦恩
受害可能性  95.42%
行凶可能性  72.98%
真不敢相信
I cannot believe this is happening!
有人在故意整我  你看不出来吗
Someone is screwing with me. Can't you see that?
即将行凶
我会解决
I'm gonna fix this.
在找人吗  放松
Looking for someone? Easy.
这么近我可不会射偏
I won't miss at this range.
你到底有什么计划
So what was the plan?
你是准备在会面之前还是之后干掉我
Were you gonna take me out before or after my meeting?
我还没想好
I hadn't decided yet.
你可给我造成了
You know, you've caused me
很大的伤害和麻烦  萨默斯先生
a great deal of pain and suffering, Mr. Sommers.
那就对了
That was the point.
现在你要帮我把一切恢复原状
Now, you're gonna help me get it all back.
克鲁格先生  你收到我的留言了
Mr. Kruger, you got my message.
出  什么事了
What...happened to you?
真高兴你问了这问题
You know, I'm... really glad you asked.
其他人去哪儿了
Where's the rest of your team?
很不幸  他们得搭早一班的飞机
Unfortunately, they had to catch an earlier flight.
他们让我代为致歉
They send their regrets.
你好
Hello.
对了  这位是萨默斯先生
Yeah. This is Mr. Sommers.
我以为我们是要讨论生意合作
Look, I thought we were gonna discuss our deal.
是啊  我给你打完电话后不久
Yes, well, shortly after I called you.
我们再次向首席执行官请示了这个问题
We attempted to revisit the issue with our CEO,
但我们没法让他改变决定
but we couldn't get him to reconsider his decision.
什么
What?
很抱歉  我以为当面谈
I'm sorry, I thought a face-to-face
比再打电话给你要合适
would be better than another phone call.
不
No.
-什么  -不
- Excuse me? - No!
你不明白我遭了多大罪才来到这里
You have no idea what I've been through to get here!
克鲁格先生  为什么你带着枪
Mr. Kruger, why do you have a gun?
因为这个人羞辱了我  盗取了我的财产
Because this man humiliated me, stole from me,
甚至还想要杀死我
and even tried to kill me.
都是他的变态游戏让我们的合作告吹了
It was his twisted little game that made our deal fall apart.
-告诉他  -好了  先把枪放下
- Tell him. - Okay, just, let's put down the gun.
我说了告诉他
I said tell him!
别动手  萨默斯先生
Don't do it, Mr. Sommers.
你是谁
Who are you?
知晓事情原委的人
Someone who knows what this is about.
克洛伊
Chloe.
那你知道  是他害死了我女儿
Then you know he killed her,
正义必须伸张
and something had to be done.
我从未动过你女儿
I never touched your daughter.
你虽然没像那个禽兽一样亲自动手
You may not have put your hands on her like that monster did,
但你罪孽相同
but you're just as guilty.
我什么都没做
I didn't do anything!
正是
Exactly.
她的前男友找到她三次
See, her ex-boyfriend found her three times--
三次都是通过你的"生活轨迹"
three times, using your LifeTrace.
每次他找到她
And every time he found her,
我们都求你的公司从网上撤下她的信息
we asked the company to take her information down,
但他们不肯
and they didn't do it,
所以他又找到了我女儿  一次又一次
and so he found her again, and again,
直到最后杀害了她
until the last time when he killed her.
就是因为你和你公司"什么都没做"
All because you and your company didn't do anything.
我不知道
I didn't know.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
是吗
Yeah?
抱歉可不够
Sorry isn't good enough.
听我说  斯图
Listen to me, Stu.
你动了手  你这辈子
You do this, and your life...
就毁了
it's over.
已经毁了
It's already over.
斯图
Stu...
不应该这样纪念你的女儿
this isn't the way to honor your daughter's memory.
好好想想  克洛伊会希望你怎么做
Think about it. What would Chloe want?
你做得对  为你们父女二人
You did the right thing, for both of you.
里瑟先生  我三角定位了
Mr. Reese, I triangulated the call
克鲁格在电梯里接到的那通电话
that Kruger received in the elevator.
信号现在在梅菲尔德内部
It's now coming from inside the Mayfield.
里瑟先生
Mr. Reese?
你说得对  正义必须伸张
You were right. Something had to be done,
所以我们才联系你  萨默斯先生
which is why we reached out to you, Mr. Sommers.
是你  是你给了我包裹
You--you did it. You sent me the package.
我们给了你  为女儿伸张正义的方法
We sent you the means to exact justice for your daughter,
你也有付诸实践的勇气
and you had the courage to act.
不幸的是  车祸没能成功
Unfortunately, the car crash wasn't successful...
只得这样即兴演出
requiring this improvisation,
不过到头来总算成功了
but everything worked out in the end.
你该离开了  萨默斯先生
You should go now, Mr. Sommers.
你现在应该理解了
I think you understand now.
理解什么
Understand what?
隐私泄露后  你会失去什么
What is lost when your privacy's stripped away.
你的身份  你的工作
Your identity, your job,
你的家庭
your family,
人身安全
security,
一切
everything.
你
You...
还有千千万万像我一样的人
And thousands more just like me.
我们不愿再沉默  而选择采取行动
People who have chosen action over apathy,
重新夺回被你这种人
to take back what men like you
和政府偷走的权利
and the government have stolen.
这不是游戏  克鲁格先生
This wasn't a game, Mr. Kruger,
这是一个教训
this was a lesson,
第一个
the first.
我们本来只想吓吓你  但是
We were just gonna scare you, but...
那改变不了什么  是吧
that wouldn't change anything, would it?
芬奇
Finch.
约翰  你中枪了吗
John, are you shot?
打在防弹衣上了  估计肋骨断了
My vest caught it. Think my rib's broken.
克鲁格呢
And Kruger?
他死了  芬奇
He's dead, Finch.
看到他了
I got him.
能走吗
Can you walk?
我得去追科利尔
I need to get to Collier.
我们得离开这儿
We've got to get you out of here.
她说得对  里瑟先生  以后再说
She's right, Mr. Reese. Another time.
还想吐
Back for more?
我有话要说
I need to say something.
先给我买杯咖啡不行吗
Can it wait until after you buy me coffee?
我知道  你必须带搭档才能上回白班
I know you had to take a partner to get back on days,
但你知不知道有两个新人
but did you know that two other rookies
是排在我之前应该跟你的
were supposed to be in this seat before me?
他们全都申请重新分配了
And both requested to be reassigned.
如果你想要换教习警员  就提出来
If you want another F.T.O., just say the word.
不  这才是重点  我没申请重新分配
No, that's the point, I didn't ask to be reassigned,
因为我想选择你
because I chose you.
选择我  为什么
Chose me? Why?
在警察学院时  我就听说过你
In the academy, I heard about you.
你在凶案组的事迹
Your work with the homicide task force
你如何推翻那些腐败警察
and how you took down those corrupt cops.
我就想
I thought,
有一天  我也想那样
"Someday, that's what I want to do."
所以我抓住机会  在你手下受教
That's why I jumped at the chance to train under you.
但我感觉你根本不愿意教习
But I don't get the sense that you want to train anybody,
如果是这样
and if that's the case,
我宁愿你甩掉我算了
then I'd prefer it if you just cut me loose.
3A10  莫里斯大街和149街交汇发生一起车祸
3-Adam-10, we got a report of a 10-53 near Morris and 149th.
收到  调度中心  3A10前往
Roger, dispatch. 3-Adam-10 responding.
我给里弗顿公司的总部打了电话
I made a call to Riverton's home office.
科利尔  当然是假名
Seems Collier, no doubt an alias,
他没回去上班
has not returned to work.
我想他也不会
And I don't think he will.
他四个月前开始担任顾客分析副总一职
He started four months ago as V.P. of customer analytics,
他可以藉此接近克鲁格
a position that allowed him to get close enough to Kruger
得以见证并参与
so that he could both witness and participate
毁掉他生活的整个过程
in the dismantling of his life.
他告诉克鲁格  还有跟他一样的人
He told Kruger there were others like him.
是啊  这点我相信他
Yes, and I'm inclined to believe him.
我发现寄给萨默斯先生
I discovered that the anonymous packages
和其他人的匿名包裹
sent to Mr. Sommers and the others
是经由邮政中心
came through mail-processing centers
发往全国的
scattered all over the country.
本来可以省掉包裹
Could've saved on the postage
逮到机会直接爆头
and just shot him when they had the chance.
我就是说  这计划煞费苦心
I'm just saying it was an elaborate plan.
这不仅是要杀死克鲁格
It wasn't just about killing Kruger.
而是要给被伤害者以报仇的机会
It was about giving the people he hurt a chance at retribution.
同时也是实践一种理念
And also putting an ideology into action.
科利尔称杀害克鲁格是"一个教训"
Collier referred to Kruger's murder as "A lesson".
第一个
The first.
不管他背后的组织
I fear that whatever his organization's
终极目标为何
ultimate goals may be,
恐怕这仅仅是开始
this could be just the beginning.